<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Machine Learning on Branden States&#39; Github Site</title>
    <link>http://brandenstates.github.io/tags/machine-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Machine Learning on Branden States&#39; Github Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://brandenstates.github.io/tags/machine-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Post Tournament Follow-Up</title>
      <link>http://brandenstates.github.io/2021/04/09/post-tournament-follow-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brandenstates.github.io/2021/04/09/post-tournament-follow-up/</guid>
      <description>https://fantasy.espn.com/tournament-challenge-bracket/2021/en/entry?entryID=48742608
So at the time of writing my last post, the round of 32 had ended and the tournament was heading into the sweet sixteen. At that point, my bracket was in the 99.4 percentile, and unfortunately, that isn’t the case anymore. My model definitely had some misses, and my human errors also cost me, but in some cases they actually helped. So lets pick things up at the sweet sixteen for each region and see where I went wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attempting to Predict March Madness with Machine Learning</title>
      <link>http://brandenstates.github.io/2021/03/27/attempting-to-predict-march-madness-with-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://brandenstates.github.io/2021/03/27/attempting-to-predict-march-madness-with-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Alright folks, here we are. The first of (hopefully) many blog posts, and this one is on a project that has been an absolute blast. For my Advanced Sports Data course, my professor gave us the assignment of using our choice of various machine learning methods to create a model to predict the outcome of men’s college basketball games based on prior data, and use that model to attempt to find the results of the NCAA tournament this year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
